anscamobile.com 2010-09-17

# Ansca | Unlock your imagination...

## Ansca Customer Privacy Policy

Ansca’s Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Ansca anytime you interact with Ansca, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase Ansca products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Ansca, and we go to great lengths to protect it. 

### Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. 

If you do not want Ansca to keep you up to date with Ansca news, software updates and the latest information on products and services, update your personal contact information and preferences. 

### What information we collect and how we may use it

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products. For example: 

  * We may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product. 
  * When you interact with Ansca, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the Ansca products you own, such as their serial numbers and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue. 
  * We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. 
  * We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them. 
  * We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Ansca’s products. 

**Your Ansca ID and related information**

The Ansca website, as well as Ansca services, allows you to create an “Ansca ID” based on your personal information. This convenient service saves you time and allows for easier use of our web services. Here’s how it works: You create a personal profile — providing your name, phone number, email address, and in some cases your mailing address or a credit card number — and choose a password and password hint (such as the month and day of your birth) for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal Ansca ID — in many cases simply your email address, because it’s unique and easy to remember. The next time you order from Ansca or register a new product, all you need to do is enter your Ansca ID and password; the system looks up the information it needs to assist you. 

**Publicly displayed information is public**

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on an Ansca website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. Ansca is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, Ansca will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available. 

### When we disclose your information

Ansca takes your privacy very seriously. Ansca does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. 

**Within the Ansca Group**

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Ansca group globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with Ansca’s privacy policy. 

**With our service providers, vendors, and strategic partners**

There are also times when it may be advantageous for Ansca to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Ansca has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Ansca to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Ansca’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Ansca website. 

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary. 

### How we protect your personal information

Ansca takes precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari. 

### Integrity of your personal information

Ansca has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date. 

### Kids

Ansca recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Ansca purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to Ansca and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. 

### Cookies and other technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Ansca’s website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Ansca will not use the information collected to market directly to that person. 

In some of our email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Ansca website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email. 

In addition we use pixel tags — tiny graphic images — to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site. 

Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to ensure that we’re sending only messages that are of interest to our customers. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to a customer. We store all of this information in a secure database located in the United States. 

### Our companywide commitment to your privacy

As we said, Ansca takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Ansca employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. 

### International users

Ansca’s website has links to the sites of other companies. Ansca is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

### Privacy questions

Ansca may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy. 

Copyright © 2009-2010 Ansca Inc. All rights reserved.   
Ansca Inc., 720 University Avenue, Suite #105, Palo Alto, CA, 94301. 

Last updated January 11th, 2010
